dashburst.com 2016-11-06

# Privacy - DashBurst

Thanks for checking out DashBurst! While you’re here, know that protecting your privacy is important to us and we are committed to being transparent with how we use your information.

Our website (dashburst.com), mobile applications and any of our services directing you to this Privacy Policy (e.g. www.dashburst.com, blog.dashburst.com, magazine.dashburst.com, developers.dashburst.com, collectively referred to as the “Site”) are controlled by DashBurst LLC (collectively “DashBurst,” "we," or "us"). This Privacy Policy also includes the text outlined in our Terms of Service https://dashburst.com/terms/.

By using any of our websites, mobile applications and services you consent to our collection, transfer, storage, disclosure and other use of your personal data as described in this Privacy Policy. You authorize DashBurst to use your information in the United States and any other country, regardless of which country you reside in or transmit information from. If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or would like to know more about how we collect and store information, or would like to know more about your options, please continue reading or contact us at: privacy@dashburst.com.

Information We Collect

Information you provide when creating a DashBurst account: When you create an account on DashBurst, you must provide login credentials like your name, email address and password, or you must authenticate by using another social service like Facebook, Twitter or Google. You may also include additional information like a profile picture, bio text, location, time zone, phone number and other social profiles. If you connect your DashBurst account to other online services, we will use that public information to help complete your DashBurst profile, which is also available to the public. At any time, you have the right to update and modify your profile, bio and contact information.

Your Contact information: In addition to using your contact information to help create your account, we may also use the information to send you notices about our services, respond to help requests, and deliver the site notifications you have subscribed to. Even though your phone number and email address may not be displayed publicly, we could use this information to help connect you with other DashBurst users. Also we require you to have a verified email address in order to upload content to DashBurst.

Your Content: DashBurst is a content-sharing platform, thus most of the content and information you share is intended to be public. This includes the content you post, like, comment on, and Reburst, as well as users you follow and other data you provide.

Location: You may choose to provide your location in your profile or enable your computer or other devices to send us your location information. We may use, store and display your location information for your profile and to tag content with a location when desired. We may also use this information for analytics, customization and other services.

Links you share: We store information about the links you share in order to facilitate our services, including web and email notifications, online sharing, third-party services, redirecting clicks, client applications and other uses.

Cookies: Similar to other online sites, we use cookie technology to collect information about website usage to help improve our services and personalize your preferences on DashBurst. What that means is that when you visit our site we may send your computer a small cookie file to collect information about your activity on DashBurst like the pages you visit, links you click, setting changes and searches. If you don’t want cookies from DashBurst or any other site, you can modify your browser settings to reject cookies, but keep in mind some services may no longer work if cookies are disabled.

Log Data: When you use DashBurst, our servers may automatically store information from your browser or mobile app including your IP address (Internet Protocol address), browser type and settings, device information, pages viewed, links clicked, information about your requests, cookie data and how you use DashBurst.

Third-Party Services: DashBurst uses several third-party providers to help facilitate our services, host our platform and better understand our services. These third-party services may also use cookies and additional technologies to collect information about you, log data, and determine how you use our services.

Please consider that the content and information you share could be broadly shared online, so you should always be careful regarding what you share.

Information Use, Sharing and Disclosure

With your consent: We may share information with your consent including information you post publicly or include in your profile. We may also share information with other services like Facebook or Twitter to which you choose to link.

Service Providers: We may employ third-party companies or individuals to process and collect information on our behalf in the United States or abroad in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Online advertisers: We may allow online advertisers and other third parties to collect information on DashBurst.

Legal Disclosures: To protect the safety, security, rights or property of the public, any person, or DashBurst, or prevent fraud or any other illegal activity, we may disclose your information if deemed necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request.

Transfer of Business: DashBurst reserves the right to engage in a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy filing, dissolution, or any other reorganization or similar transaction that may require the transfer of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

Your Information Collection and Use Options

You can choose to not provide us with certain personal information. However, if you choose to not provide certain personal information, certain functions of our platform and other member features may not be available to you. You can also control which notifications you receive from DashBurst on the web and through email via your account notifications page and other app or device-level settings. For operational purposes, we may still send you other transactional and administrative email communications without offering you the ability to opt-out.

You can unlink your DashBurst account from other services and close your account at any time where we will then deactivate your account and make your profile and Bursts unavailable. We may, however, retain copies of Bursts previously shared online for legal purposes (like to help prevent fraud and other illegal activity) as well as other purposes. You can still reactivate your account at any time. Also, if information has already been shared with third-party services, the retention will be subject to those third-party policies.

Information Protection and Security

We take protecting your information very seriously and want you to feel confident using our services for personal or business purposes. We employ several security measures to help safeguard your personal information and privacy including encryption, firewalls and restricted access to your data. However we do not promise that your personal information, activity, searches or any other communications will always remain secure. You should always avoid sending or disclosing sensitive information online.

User Submissions

We provide several areas on the site for you to post information about yourself, communicate with others, and upload various types of content (e.g. text, photos, videos, audio files, documents, and infographics). Anything posted on our site is governed by our Terms of Service and may appear on other websites and searches. Also, anything you voluntarily post or disclose in publicly viewable areas on DashBurst is visible to the world and can be collected by others, so please use discretion.

Privacy of Children

DashBurst is not intended for use by children under the age of 13, nor do we knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.

Third-Party Rights

Our Privacy Policy does not give rights to third parties to enforce or disclose any personal information relating to users of this site.

Privacy Policy Changes

We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time as needed. If we do so these changes will be posted to this page and, if you continue to use the site afterward, you agree to the changes of the revised policy. If we make significant changes that affect how we collect and use your information, we may provide you a notice by email or ask for your consent in accordance with the law.

Effective: June 17, 2015
